Guide to the photograph album 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection AD.MC.030_ref165
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection, 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165 (Box Electronic Records, E-records AD_MC_030_ref165)
  - Top: A clipping entitled 'Upper-Egypt Luxor,' with a view of the Luxor Temple. Bottom Left: A clipping with the text "Cario: Bazaar in the Mousky." Bottom Right: A clipping with the text "Luxor: Statues of Ramesses II" (two statues of Ramesses II in the Temple of Luxor)., February 1929; AD_MC_03
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Furnishings; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Cairo, Egypt; Markets; Shops; Workers; Lanterns/Lamps; Streets/Roads; Facial Hair; Signs/Signposts; Printed Materials
  - Two views of the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000039_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Luxor, Egypt; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture
  - Two views of the statues of Ramesses II, and a woman sitting between two columns in the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000040_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; Luxor, Egypt; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Two postcards of the pillars of Amenhotep III in the Luxor Temple. Top: (No.203) Luxor Papyrus Pillar of Amenhotep III. Bottom: (No. 1501) Luxor Temple: Papyrus Pillars of Amenhotep III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000041_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Temples; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Luxor, Egypt
  - Two postcards of the pillars of Amenhotep III in the Luxor Temple. Top: Luxor: The Papyrus Columns of Amenhotep III. Bottom: (No. 1508) Luxor-Temple: Papyrus Columns of Amen Hotep III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000042_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Palm Trees; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - A postcard with the text "Luxor Temple: The Colonnade.", February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000043_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Temples; Mosques; Religious Sites; Luxor, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Regional/National Dress
  - Top: A woman next to the statues in the Luxor Temple. Bottom: Two postcards. Left: (No.1505) Luxor Temple: Wife of Ramesses II. Right: (No.1506) Luxor Temple: Statue of Ramesses II., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000044_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Deserts; Mountains/Hills; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Gelatin Silver Prints; Unknown
  - Two postcards. Top: Luxor Temple: The Forecourt and Statues of Rameses II. Bottom: (No.1503) Luxor Temple: Pylon and Obelisk., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000045_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Architecture; Temples; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Men; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Two postcards. Top: Luxor. Pylon Statues and Obelisk of Ramesses II. Bottom: (No.1504) Luxor - Mosque of Sheikh Abu el Haggag (a postcard of the Abou al-Haggag Mosque)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000046_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Temples; Donkeys; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Transportation; Animals; Men; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Individual Portraits; Mosques; Religious Sites; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: (No.1511) Luxor: Nilesteamers and Winter Palace Hotel. Bottom: Two views of different reliefs both representing Min, the god of fertility., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000047_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Nile River; Rivers; Men; Children; Boys; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Coast; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Hotels; Buildings; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures
  - Top: (No. 1510) Luxor: Crossing the Nile (a postcard of a sailboat crossing the Nile River). Bottom Left: a hieroglyphic relief. Bottom Right: columns in the Luxor Temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000048_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Boats/Ships; Men; Group Portraits; Water; Coast; Transportation; Nile River; Rivers; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: (No.1529) Thebes: Der-El-Bahari, Temple of Queen Hatshepsut. Bottom: A view of the Temple of Hatshepsut., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000049_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Camels; Animals; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Luxor, Egypt; Landscapes
  - Two views of the Temple of Hatshepsut., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000050_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Crowds; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Landscapes
  - Top: A clipping with the text 'Upper-Egypt Thebes.' Bottom Left: Karnak: The Hypostyle Hall. Bottom Right: A man with two children in front of the Colossi of Memnon., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000051_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Boys; Children; Streets/Roads; Group Portraits; Thebes, Egypt; Postcards; Printed Materials
  - No. 1524 Thebes: The Colossi of Memnon (a postcard of two men on the road to the Colossi of Memnon)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000052_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Landscapes; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Thebes, Egypt; Postcards
  - (No.1532) Thebes: Part of the Ramesseum and the greatest Statue of Ramesses II., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000053_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1525) Thebes: the Ramesseum. Bottom Left: (No. 1526)Thebes: the Ramesseum - Statue of Ramesses. Bottom Right: (No. 1527) Thebes: the Ramesseum reliefs., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000054_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Postcards; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Statues/Sculptures; Mountains/Hills; Deserts; Men; Individual Portraits; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Edfu, Egypt
  - Two men near a hillside with exposed rock-cut tombs at the Tomb of the Nobles, Luxor., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000055_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Men; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egypt; Tents
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1534) Thebes: Medinet Habu - statue of the goddess. Middle: (No. 1533) Thebes: Medinet Habu - The Temple of Rameses III. Bottom: (No. 1535) Thebes: Medinet Habu - The Pavillion of the Temple of Rameses III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000056_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Turbans; Hats; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Group Portraits; Egypt
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000057_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: A clipping with the text 'Upper-Egypt Karnak.' Bottom: (No.1514) Karnak: Ptolomey - Gateway and the Temple of Khonsu., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000058_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Photographic Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Palm Trees; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Temples; Luxor, Egypt; Donkeys; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Buildings
  - A blank page in the 'Egypt and Sudan Post Card Album' compiled by Edith and William P. Lincoln - Hisham Khatib Collection., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000059_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
  - Top: Karnak: The Amun Temple. Bottom: Two views of the Statue of Amun Ra at Karnak Temple, Luxor, Egypt., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000060_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Statues/Sculptures; Buildings; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Two postcards. Top: (No.1527) Karnak: The Great Temple of Amun Ra and the Sacred Lake. Bottom: (No.1512) Karnak: The Great Temple of Amun Ra., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000061_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Lakes; Water; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Landscapes; Luxor, Egypt; Streets/Roads
  - Top: (No.1516) Karnak: The Temple of Amun Ra. Bottom: Karnak: Central view of the Great Temple of Amun Ra., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000062_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Temples; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Streets/Roads; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: (No.1520) Karnak: The Temple of Rameses III. Bottom: a view of two people near the statues in the Temple of Rameses III., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000063_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Temples; Luxor, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Men; Women; Hats; Group Portraits; Bags/Purses; Head Covers/Veils
  - Top: Reliefs on a temple's facade. Bottom: A woman standing in a temple., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000064_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Temples; Egypt
  - Three postcards. Top: (No.1523) Karnak: the Temple of Opet. Bottom Left: (No. 1518) Karnak: The Hypostyle Hall. Bottom Right: (No.1519) Karnak: Pillars in the Great Hypostyle Hall., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000065_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Men; Regional/National Dress; Camels; Animals; Turbans; Hats; Individual Portraits; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Buildings; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt
  - Top: (No.1513) Karnak: Memorials of Thotmes III. Bottom: An Egyptian relief depicting animals and plants from the botanical garden wall at the Temple of Karnak., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000066_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Luxor, Egypt; Animals
  - (No.1517,1515) Two postcards. Karnak: Avenue of the Sphinxes., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000067_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Palm Trees; Landscapes; Men; Donkeys; Regional/National Dress; Animals; Mountains/Hills; Boys; Children; Individual Portraits; Luxor, Egypt
  - Three views of the Avenue of the Sphinxes in Karnak., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000068_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Landscapes; Palm Trees; Mountains/Hills; Luxor, Egypt; Horses; Animals; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Individual Portraits; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Regional/National Dress
  - Three group portraits of people in front of tents., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000069_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Egypt; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boys; Children; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Canes/Walking Sticks; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Tents
  - Top and Middle: Two views of sailboats with passengers. Bottom: A group of men in the desert., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000070_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water; Mountains/Hills; Egypt; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Boys; Children; Turbans; Head Covers/Veils; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Deserts
  - Two views of the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000071_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Streets/Roads; Tents; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Mountains/Hills; Architecture; Men; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Fez/Tarboush; Luxor, Egypt; Tombs/Mausoleums
  - Top: A view of King Tutankhamen's Tomb. Bottom: A road in the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000072_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; English Writing; Buildings; Men; Uniforms; Fez/Tarboush; Regional/National Dress; Hats; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Luxor, Egypt; Group Portraits
  - A view of the first coffin and sarcophagus of King Tutankhamen., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000073_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Coffins/Caskets; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Tombs/Mausoleums; Luxor, Egypt; English Writing
  - A postcard showing the mural paintings in Tomb 9 of Ramesses V and VI., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000074_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums; Paintings; English Writing; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Luxor, Egypt; Postcards
  - A postcard of the mural paintings in the side chamber of the Tomb of Seti I in the Valley of the Kings., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000075_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Paintings; Tombs/Mausoleums; Luxor, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Boats/Ships; Transportation
  - A postcard of a mural painting from the Tomb of Rameses I., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000076_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Paintings; Tombs/Mausoleums; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Animals; Luxor, Egypt
  - A view of a bridge and people standing on the bank of a river., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000077_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bridges; Streets/Roads; Water; Crowds; Landscapes; Egypt
  - Two group portraits of a crowd., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000078_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Egypt; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Hats; Men; Children; Boys; Crowds; Fez/Tarboush; Palm Trees; Streets/Roads; Street Lamps; Girls
  - Top: A clipping with the text 'Upper-Egypt Edfou-Komombo.' Bottom Left: (No.1570) Edfou: Reliefs of the Temple of Horus. Bottom Right: (No.1569) Edfou: the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000079_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Printed Materials; Edfu, Egypt; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1572) Edfou: Pillar-vestibule of the Temple of Horus. Bottom Left: (No.1568) Edfou: the Temple of Horus. Bottom Right: (No.1571) Edfou: Part of the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000080_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Statues/Sculptures; Men; Regional/National Dress; Individual Portraits; Architecture; Buildings; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Egyptian Hieroglyphics
  - Two views of the columns and reliefs at the Temple of Horus, Edfu., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000081_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Edfu, Egypt; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Hats
  - Three postcards. Top: (No. 1572) Edfou: Pillar-vestibule of the Temple of Horus. Bottom Left: (No.1568) Edfou: the Temple of Horus. Bottom Right: (No.1571) Edfou: Part of the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000082_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Temples; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Edfu, Egypt
  - A newspaper clipping with the text 'Portion of the outer wall at the Temple of Komombo. Showing a table of surgical instruments representing the clinic of Imhotep, god of medicine.', February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000083_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Printed Materials; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Edfu, Egypt; Temples; Statues/Sculptures
  - Top: (No. 1573) Edfou: The Temple of Horus. Bottom: A woman sitting at the Temple of Horus., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000084_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Women; Hats; Individual Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Buildings; Architecture; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Deserts; Edfu, Egypt
  - Top: (No. 1575) Kom-Ombo: The Temple of Ombo. Bottom: Kom-Ombo: General View., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000085_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Water; Boats/Ships; Temples; Architecture; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Transportation; Buildings; Aswan, Egypt
  - A newspaper clipping showing a relief in the Temple of Kom Ombo with the text, "The gods Thoth and Horus pouring the water of life over the king. A carving on the walls of the Temple of Komombo.", February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000086_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Printed Materials; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Aswan, Egypt
  - Top: A view of the Temple of Kom Ombo from afar. Bottom Left: (No.1578) Komombo: Ptolomey between the two Divinities of Upper and Lower Egypt. Bottom Right: (No. 1577) Komombo: God Horus writing the Life of Philometer., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000087_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Temples; Landscapes; Water; Aswan, Egypt; Postcards; Men; Boys; Children; Regional/National Dress; Turbans; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Architecture; Buildings; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Statues/Sculptures; Rivers; Nile River
  - Top: (No. 1576) Kom-Ombo: The Temple of Ombos seen from the Nile. Bottom: (No. 1574) Kom-Ombo: the Temple of Ombos., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000088_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Nile River; Rivers; Men; Children; Group Portraits; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Aswan, Egypt; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Statues/Sculptures; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Water
  - Top: A cutout depicting the Nile steamers 'Delta' and 'Thebes.' Bottom: The front cover of the passenger list for Cook's Nile Services steamer 's.s. Thebes' (linked ref 89_02)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000089_000001; Thomas Cook and Son Ltd; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Mountains/Hills; Nile River; Rivers; Water; Flags; Printed Materials; Men; Women; Children; Donkeys; Animals
  - Top: A cutout depicting the Nile steamers 'Delta' and 'Thebes.' Bottom: The passenger list for Cook's Nile Services steamer 's.s. Thebes' (linked ref 89_01)., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000089_000002; Thomas Cook and Son Ltd; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Printed Materials; Boats/Ships; Transportation; Travel; Nile River; Rivers
  - From the top left clockwise: A man holding a donkey, the Temple of Kom Ombo from afar, a man leaning on columns while holding a sword, and a postcard (No. 1579) Kom-Ombo: Crowning of Philometer., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000090_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Postcards; Individual Portraits; Men; Regional/National Dress; Fez/Tarboush; Hats; Workers; Uniforms; Donkeys; Animals; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Flags; Temples; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Architecture; Buildings; Nile River; Rivers; Statues/Sculptures; Egyptian Hieroglyphics; Swords/Knives; Weapons; Facial Hair
  - From the top left clockwise: A man holding a donkey, the Temple of Kom Ombo from afar, a man leaning on columns while holding a sword, and a postcard (No. 1579) Kom-Ombo: Crowning of Philometer., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000091_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)
    Photographic Prints; Postcards; Men; Individual Portraits; Regional/National Dress; Water; Aswan, Egypt; Buildings; Palm Trees; Camlica Hill, Istanbul, Turkey; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Nile River; Rivers; Architecture
  - Top: A clipping with the text 'Upper-Egypt Assouan.' Bottom: (No. 1536) Aswan seen from Elephantine Island., February 1929; AD_MC_030_ref165_000092_000001; 1 Photographic Prints (Box Electronic Records)